// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How old _____ you?",
    answer: "are",
    options: [
      "is",
      "am",
      "are",
      "do"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Ten plus twelve is _____ .",
    answer: "twenty-two",
    options: [
      "twenty-twelve",
      "twenty-two",
      "twenty-second",
      "twenty-too"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I saw three small _____ .",
    answer: "childrens",
    options: [
      "children's",
      "children",
      "childs",
      "childrens"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Lucy _____ like dancing.",
    answer: "doesn't",
    options: [
      "isn't",
      "doesn't",
      "don't",
      "haven't"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Excuse me, _____ time is it?",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "why",
      "when",
      "which",
      "what"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "_____ live in China.",
    answer: "The Chinese",
    options: [
      "The Chinese",
      "The China",
      "The Chinish",
      "The Chin's"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What's _____ name?",
    answer: "her",
    options: [
      "hier",
      "hear",
      "hair",
      "her"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "_____ are three computers in my school.",
    answer: "There",
    options: [
      "They",
      "Their",
      "There",
      "These"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What time is it? Look at your _____.",
    answer: "watch",
    options: [
      "witch",
      "watch",
      "wash",
      "wish"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "I have my English classes _____ Monday.",
    answer: "every",
    options: [
      "ever",
      "never",
      "every",
      "each"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "I didn't _____ coffee yesterday.",
    answer: "drank",
    options: [
      "drinked",
      "drank",
      "drink",
      "drunk"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "This isn't your jacket. It's _____ .",
    answer: "mine",
    options: [
      "mine",
      "me",
      "my",
      "myself"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Andy doesn’t want to go to the beach, because he _____ swim.",
    answer: "can't",
    options: [
      "do",
      "musn't",
      "didn't",
      "can't"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "_____ sugar do you put in your tea?",
    answer: "How much",
    options: [
      "How many",
      "How much",
      "How any",
      "Any much"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Are you going to the café? _____ with you.",
    answer: "I'll come",
    options: [
      "I'll come",
      "I'm come",
      "I come",
      "I go"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Can you _____ a photo of us, please?",
    answer: "take",
    options: [
      "do",
      "make",
      "bake",
      "take"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "I hate waiting _____ people who are late.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [
      "for",
      "of",
      "to",
      "at"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "This exercise is not difficult. It's very _____!",
    answer: "easy",
    options: [
      "ease",
      "easy",
      "esy",
      "eased"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Laura is a movie star. She is an _____.",
    answer: "actress",
    options: [
      "acting",
      "actor",
      "actress",
      "act"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Hurry up ow we'll _____ our train!",
    answer: "miss",
    options: [
      "cancel",
      "fail",
      "leave",
      "miss"
    ]
  },
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

];